Previously on Friends...
Erica, are... are you okay?
Yeah. You know,
maybe I ate too much.
I keep getting
these stomachaches.
They come and go,
like, every few minutes.
Oh, my God!
Relax. We'll just
get her some antacids.
She doesn't have a stomachache!
She's in labor!
Oh, my God!
So if you think
that I didn't
say good-bye to you
because you don't
mean as much to me
as everybody else,
you're wrong.
It's because you
mean more to me.
Rach!
What?
Hey.
Shh! Go back to sleep.
I have to go home.
Oh, God.
This was amazing.
It really was.
You've learned
some new moves.
Yeah, well, this guy at work
gave me Sex For Dummies
as a joke.
Who's laughing now?
I know.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Okay, breathe.
breathe, breathe.
Oh!
Okay, good.
Next time,
can I say breathe?
No. Last time, you said it like
Dracula, and it scared her.
Can I get
you anything?
You want some more ice chips?
No. I'm okay.
All right,
I'll be right back.
Where you going?
To use the bathroom.
You can't leave me
alone with her.
What?
This is exactly the kind
of social situation
that I am not
comfortable with.
What kind of social situation
are you comfortable with?
It's just that
we've never spent
any time, you know,
alone together.
You'll be fine.
Nah, you won't, but I'll
be back in two minutes.
Okay.
So, uh... any plans
for the summer?
I don't know.
Maybe church camp.
Hah!
May not want to mention this.
So, you ever wonder
which is worse?
You know, going through labor
or getting kicked in the nuts?
What?
Oh, it's just interesting,
you know?
Because no one will ever know,
because no one
can experience both.
One of life's great
unanswerable questions.
I mean, who knows?
Maybe there's something
even more painful
than those things.
Like this.
( knocking )
Come in.
Morning.
Hey.
What's that?
It's my housewarming present
for Monica and Chandler.
( chirping )
Oh! Oh, it's a baby
chick and duck.
Uh-huh. And I named them
Chick Jr. and Duck Jr.
I did not
see that coming.
Yeah, yeah.
I figured they'd love it
at the new house, you know?
It has that big backyard.
And then,
when they get old,
they can go
to that special farm
that Chandler took
the other chick and duck to.
Yes.
You know, it's a shame
people can't visit there.
That is
the rule though.
Yeah.
Guess what!
You're
almost an uncle.
What?
Yeah. Erica went
into labor last night;
Monica and Chandler
are at the hospital right now.
Oh, my God!
And I have
a definite feeling
it's going to be a girl.
Phoebe, you were sure
Ben was going
to be a girl.
Have you seen him
throw a ball?
Is Rachel here?
Uh, I think
she's still asleep.
Hey, hey, hey. How
did it go with you
guys last night?
She seemed pretty
pissed at you.
We, uh... you know,
we worked things out.
What's
that smile?
Did something happen
with you two?
Hey, I'm not one
to kiss and tell.
But I'm also not one to have sex
and shut up.
We totally did it!
Oh, my God!
You and Rachel?
I know. Isn't
this pretty great?
So what does that mean?
Are you guys
getting back together?
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, we didn't
really get to talk.
But do you want
to get back together?
I don't know.
It was incredible.
I mean, it just felt so right.
When I was holding her,
I mean, I... I never
wanted to let her go.
You know what? Yeah, I do.
I want to be together.
Yay!
Shh!
Hey, hey, hey.
So... so, is she
still going to Paris?
Well, I haven't thought of that.
I... I hope not.
This is like the
best day ever. Ever!
You guys might
get back together.
Monica and Chandler
are getting their baby.
There are chicks and ducks
in the world again. Oh!
I feel like I'm in a musical.
( humming intro )
♪ When the sun comes up
bright and beaming ♪
♪ And the moon
comes... ♪
Morning.
Guess you'll never
know how it ends.
Hey.
Hi.
How did you sleep?
Good. You?
Good.
I'll bet
you did.
Uh... would you guys
mind giving us a minute?
Sure. Yeah.
Will you just
keep an eye
on the chick
and the duck?
Chick and the duck?
Didn't they die?
Dive.
Yeah, they dove...
headfirst into
fun on the farm.
So...
Morning.
You, too.
Last night was
just wonderful.
It really was.
I woke up today
with the biggest smile
on my face.
Yeah. Me, too.
It was...
You know, it was, like,
one of those things
you think is never going
to happen, and then it does,
and it's everything
you want it to be.
Mm-hmm. I know.
It was just...
Oh, just the perfect
way to say good-bye.
( groaning )
Just a little
bit more, honey.
Hell, man,
this hurts!
Really? That bad?
Uh-huh. I think it's time
to kick you in the nuts
and see which is worse.
The baby's head is crowning.
Oh, my God!
That is the most
beautiful top of a
head I have ever seen.
Chandler, you
have to see this.
I'm okay.
Chandler, you don't
want to miss this.
This is the birth
of your child.
It's the miracle
of life.
All right.
Wow. That is one
disgusting miracle.
Start pushing.
There you go.
Here come
the shoulders.
( baby crying )
It's a boy.
Wow.
Is he okay?
He's just fine.
You did it.
It's a baby.
A beautiful
little baby.
And some other stuff
I'm going to pretend
I don't see.
Would you like to
cut the umbilical cord?
Well, that's spongy.
Oh...
Hey, handsome.
Oh, I'm going
to love you so much
that no woman
is ever going
to be good
enough for you.
Oh, we're so lucky.
I know.
He has your eyes.
I mean, I know
that's not possible,
but he does.
We'll just get him
cleaned up a bit.
MONICA:
Oh, my God.
He's beautiful.
Thank you so much.
I'm really happy for you guys.
How do you feel?
I'm tired.
You don't have that
much time to relax.
The other one will
be along in a minute.
I... I'm sorry?
Who should be along
in a what, now?
The next baby should
be along in a minute.
We only ordered one.
You know it's twins, right?
Oh, yeah. These are
the faces of two
people in the know.
I can't believe you
didn't know it's twins.
This has never happened before.
Well, gosh, that
makes me feel so
special and good.
Wait. Did you
know it was twins?
Yeah. It's here in the paperwork
we got from the clinic in Ohio.
Did anybody tell you?
I don't think so.
Although they did mention
something about two heartbeats.
But I thought that
was just mine and the baby's.
They kept saying both
heartbeats are really strong.
And I thought, well, that's
good, 'cause I'm having a baby.
This is unbelievable.
Twins actually run in my family.
Interesting.
Can I see you
for a second?
What do we do?
What do you mean,
what do we do?
Twins.
Chandler, you're panicking.
Uh-huh.
Join me, won't you?
Okay, what do you
say we keep one
and then just, like,
have an option
on the other one?
Chandler,
we can't split them up.
Why not?
We could give each
of them half a medallion.
And then, years later,
they'll find each other...
and be reunited.
I mean, that's a great
day for everybody.
Okay, what
if the person
who adopts the other
one is horrible?
What if they're not?
What if it's
adopted by a king?
Yeah, because I hear the king
is looking to adopt.
Monica, we're not ready
to have two babies.
That doesn't matter.
We have waited
so long for this.
I don't care
if it's two babies.
I don't care if
it's three babies.
I don't care
if the entire cast
of Eight is Enough
comes out of there.
We are taking them home
because they are our children.
Okay. Shh!
Okay.
Okay!
It looks like we're
about ready over here.
Come on, Erica,
start pushing again now.
Oh! Oh!
Here she comes.
She? It's a girl?
Yeah.
Well, now we have
one of each!
And that's enough.
And then she said it was
the perfect way to say good-bye.
Oh, my God.
What did you say?
Nothing.
What do you say
to that?
Ross, you've got to
tell her how you feel.
No way.
You can't just give up.
Is that what
a dinosaur would do?
What?
Dude, I'm just trying
to speak your language.
Ross, Rachel doesn't know
that you even want
to get back together.
If she did, she might
feel differently.
She might not even go.
You really think so?
I'm telling you.
Oh! Okay,
this is the part
of the musical
where there'd be
a really good,
convincing song.
♪ Bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
♪ Don't take no for an answer
bum-bum-bum ♪
♪ Don't let love fly away,
bum-bum-bum-bum. ♪
Hi.
Can't a girl finish
a song around here?
Hey.
Hi. So I just dropped
Emma off at my mom's.
Okay.
You're not taking her
with you tonight?
No, we decided
that I would go ahead
and set up first,
and then my mom would bring Emma
to Paris on Sunday.
Wow, eight-hour flight
with a one-year-old.
Good luck, mom.
Eight hours with my mother
talking about Atkins?
Good luck, Emma.
All right, you know what?
You're right.
I should at least
tell her how I feel.
Ross, wait, wait.
What? What?
Could you get me a muffin?
Rachel?
Yeah?
I-I know you're
leaving tonight,
but I just have
to tell you...
I love you.
I don't know if that changes
your plans at all, but...
I thought you should know.
Gunther...
Oh, I love you, too.
Probably not
in the same way,
but I do.
And when I'm in a cafe
having coffee,
or I see a man with hair
brighter than the sun,
I'll think of you.
Oh.
Oh!
Bye, you guys.
Bye.
Oh, my God!
Unbelievable.
Hey, you know
what might help?
I'm not getting you a muffin!
Do you think they recognize
each other from in there?
Maybe.
Unless they're
like two people
who've lived
in apartments
next to each other
for years
and then one day
they're pushed
through a vagina
and they meet.
We're going to take Erica
to recovery now.
MONICA:
There's something
that we wanted to tell you.
We decided to name
the girl baby Erica.
Oh, my God.
That's just like my name!
Son of a gun, it is.
Anyway, I'm going
to go get some rest.
I'm really glad
I picked you guys.
You're going
to make great parents.
Even Chandler.
Okay, well bye.
Bye.
We'll call you.
Okay.
Have fun at church camp.
Oh, look at
these little buddies.
I know.
You ready to trade?
Okay.
Oh, wait, let's see.
Take this little baby...
Okay...
We could trade later.
Yeah, I'm good.
Hey, what are you
working on?
Oh, it's a welcome-home sign
for the baby.
How sweet.
Oh, is that the baby?
No, I sat in the paint.
Hey.
So did you talk to Rachel?
No, and I'm not going to.
What?
Why not?
Because, she's just
going to shoot me down.
You guys saw what
happened with Gunther.
That did not look like fun.
How can you compare
yourself to Gunther?
I mean, sure, he's sexy
in a more obvious way.
But you have a relationship
with her.
You slept together last night.
Yeah, and she still wants to go.
It's pretty clear
where she is.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I mean, sometimes...
Uh, Joe.
Damn it!
Look, even if I were
going to tell her,
I don't have to do it now.
Okay, I'll be seeing
her again; we've got time.
No, you don't.
She's going to Paris.
She is going
to meet somebody.
Do you know how many hot guys
there are in Paris?
It's a city of Gunthers.
Hey.
PHOEBE:
What do you have there?
Oh, I made a little something.
If I had more time
to work on it,
it'd be better, but...
Oh, my God.
You did that yourself?
Honey, that's gorgeous.
You know, the baby
can't read, Mike.
Hi! You guys, the car service
just got here.
I can't believe
they're not home yet.
I have to catch my stupid plane.
I want to see the baby.
Monica just called
from the cab.
She said they
should be here
any minute.
And apparently there's
some big surprise.
Yeah, but does she sound happy
about it?
Because my friend Ethel's baby
was born
with a teeny-tiny beard.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Hi.
Oh, my gosh.
Hey.
Hi.
( gasps )
Hey, so what
is the big surprise?
Oh!
( gasps )
Oh, my God.
Okay, okay, okay,
awkward question:
The hospital knows
you took two, right?
Yes. It's twins.
Oh, they're so cute.
Now, what kinds are they?
This is a boy
and that's a girl.
Her name is Erica.
Hey, that pregnant girl's name
was Erica.
Yeah. It's a shame
you two didn't get
to spend more
time together.
We named the boy Jack
after Dad.
Oh, he's going
to be so happy.
Jack Bing--
I love that.
Ooh, it sounds like
a '40s newspaper guy,
you know, Jack Bing,
Morning Gazette.
"I'm going to blow
this story wide open."
Wow.
Oh, my gosh.
So beautiful.
I want one.
Oh, yeah?
Well, tell me which one,
I'll try to slip it
in my coat.
Seriously.
Want to make
one of those?
One? How about
a whole bunch?
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, we can teach them
to sing
and we can be like
the von Trapp family.
Only without the Nazis.
Although, that sounds
kind of dull.
Oh, you guys.
I can't believe this.
If I don't leave now
I'm going to miss my plane.
I'm just so glad you
got to see the babies.
Me, too.
I'm just sorry I'm not going
to be around
to watch you two attempt
to handle this.
All right.
I can't say good-bye
to you guys again.
I love you
all so much.
Love you.
Call us
when you get there.
I will.
Ross, come here.
I just want you to know,
last night...
I'll never forget it.
And neither will I.
All right, now I
really have to go.
Okay.
Au revoir.
Oh!
They're going to really
hate me over there.
So you just let her go?
Yeah.
Hey, maybe that's
for the best.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You know, you just--
look, you got to...
you got to think about
last night the way she
does, okay?
You know, maybe...
maybe sleeping together
was the perfect way
to say good-bye.
Now she'll never
know how he feels.
But maybe that's okay,
you know?
Maybe...
Maybe it is better this way.
I mean, now...
now you can move on.
I mean, you've been
trying to for so long.
Maybe now that you're on
different continents...
Right?
Maybe now you can
actually do it, you know?
You can...
You can
finally get over her.
Yeah, that's true.
Except...
I don't want
to get over her.
What?
I don't.
I want to be with her.
Really?
Yeah, I'm going
to go after her.
Yeah, you are!
PHOEBE:
Hey, wait.
Get your coat!
My coat.
This is so cool!
I have no idea
what's going on,
but I am excited!
Ross, Ross!
What do you think
she's going to say?
I don't know.
But look, even
if she shoots me down,
at least I won't spend
the rest of my life
wondering what
would have happened.
Where is my coat?!
You didn't bring one!
My cab's downstairs.
I'll drive you to the airport.
Wish me luck.
Hurry!
Good luck!
Okay.
There's no seat belt.
That's okay.
If we hit anything,
the engine will explode,
so, you know, it's better
if you're thrown from the car.
All right, all right.
Let's do this.
Okay.
Hey.
80th and East End.
No, I don't take passengers.
Hey, the law says
you have to accept any fare.
No, you don't understand.
This isn't a real cab.
I'm going to report you.
What's your medallion number?
My medallion number is
"Get out of the cab!"
What?
Get out of the cab!
( yelling )
Oh, hey, hey.
Can I give you guys
your housewarming present now?
Now that you can do.
All right.
Ah...
Chick, Jr.?
Duck, Jr...
Don't hide from Mama!
( groans )
You can open your eyes now.
Are we off the bridge?
Yes.
Is the old woman on the bicycle
still alive?
Yeah, she jumped right back up.
Oh, my God.
Phoebe, slow down!
Do you want to get
to Rachel in time?
Yes, but I don't want to die
in your cab.
You should have thought of that
before you got in.
Toll booth.
What?
Toll booth!
Four bucks.
There are quarters
in the glove compartment.
Hurry!
( startled yell )
Okay.
( yells )
Damn, that window's clean.
Quack, quack.
Tweet, tweet.
Quack, tweet, quack.
We were wondering what was
taking so long with the gift,
but now we understand
you were doing this.
Okay, I wanted
to surprise you, but...
for your housewarming gift,
I got you a baby chick
and a baby duck.
Really?
You got us a chick and a duck?
Oh, great.
Just what you want
for a new house
with infants--
bird feces.
But they must have
jumped off the table,
'cause now they're gone.
Don't worry,
we'll find them.
Actually, I'm going to
go check on the twins.
Oh, God!
What did I just step on?
It's okay, it's
just an egg roll.
Oh.
You stepped on my egg roll?!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know to look for
Chinese food on the floor.
Just put it on
a plate and leave.
Okay.
Let's find these birds.
All right.
( chirping )
Wait, you hear that?
( gasps )
They're in the table!
Well, that can't be good.
We've got to get them
out of there.
How?
Oh. Oh.
Maybe we can lure them out.
You know any bird calls?
Oh, tons.
I'm quite the woodsman.
Well, uh...
maybe we can just
tip the table a little.
Joey, wait!
The ball!
Oh!
( ball clanging )
( clanks )
( chirping )
Oh, God!
( sighs )
So what do we do?
I don't know, maybe we
can open this up somehow.
Okay.
No.
It's all glued together.
That mean
we have to bust it open?
I don't know, maybe.
Oh, my God.
I know, it's...
it's the foosball table.
All right, you know what?
We don't have a choice.
It's like I would have said
in that sci-fi movie
if had gotten the part...
Those are our men in there.
We have to get them out.
Even if I have to sacrifice
the most important thing
in my life--
my time machine.
Did that movie ever get made?
It did not.
Ross, where you going?
To talk to Rachel.
Isn't that why we took a ride
in the death cab?
What are you gonna do,
just walk up to her at the gate?
Have you never chased anyone
through the airport before?
Not since my cop show
got canceled.
You have to get a ticket
to get past security.
What?
We're never gonna make it.
Not with that attitude.
Now haul ass.
Okay, if you could all walk
slower that'd be great.
Madame.
Your passport, please?
Oh, my God.
I was so afraid
I wasn't going to remember
any of my high school French,
but I understood
every word you just said.
Your boarding pass, please?
Oh.
Shoot, I had it.
Oh, I can't believe this.
Madame, if you don't have...
I have it, I have it!
I have it!
Oh.
Okay, I can't find it.
But I remember
that I was in seat 32C...
because that's my bra size.
Madame, you must have
your boarding pass.
Okay, fine.
But you know what?
If I was in 36D we would not
be having this problem.
Hi, I need a ticket.
Just one?
I drive you all
the way down here,
I don't get to see
how it works out?
Fine, two tickets.
I need two tickets.
We're on our honeymoon.
And the destination?
I don't care,
whatever's the cheapest.
I'm so lucky
I married you.
Oh, shoot!
Damn it.
Where is it?
Oh, oh. I found it!
I found it!
Ha! Ha! I found it!
I told you I would find it.
In your face!
You're a different person.
Okay.
Flight 421 to Paris.
I don't see it.
Do you see it?
No, did we miss it?
No, no, no.
It's impossible.
It doesn't leave
for another 20 minutes.
Well, we have the
flight number wrong.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Here's Ross.
Hey.
Hey, listen...
Oh, my God.
Ross, you wouldn't believe
the cute little noises
the twins are making.
Listen.
Monica...
Monica.
Monica. Monica.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Shoot, they were
doing it before.
That's all right.
Listen, listen...
Wait, wait.
Here they go again.
Monica. Monica.
Monica?
Isn't that cute?
That was precious!
Listen.
I need Rachel's
flight information.
Oh, okay.
All right, it's Flight 421.
Leaves at 8:40.
Yes, that's what I have.
It's not on the board.
That's what it says here.
Flight 421 leaves at 8:40.
Newark Airport.
What?
Why, where are you?
JFK.
( shouting ):
Don't worry, you guys!
We're going to get you
out of there!
And we're also going
to buy you tiny bird
hearing aids.
Okay...
here goes.
What's the matter?
I need to say good-bye
to the table first.
I understand.
Okay...
( sighs )
Table...
you have given us
so many great times.
And you guys,
Jordan, Victor, Joel,
all of you guys...
what can I say?
You guys make us look good.
You want to say anything?
I don't know.
( sighs )
Except that,
for one last time...
Good game.
Good game. Good game.
Yeah, yeah.
Good game.
Okay, here we go.
I can't do it.
Well, I can't
do it, either.
Hey, did you find them?
Yeah, they're stuck
inside the table.
Yeah, and we have
to bust it open,
but neither of us can do it.
Aw... well, sure.
It's got to be so hard.
I'll do it. Give me!
ROSS:
Phoebe!
PHOEBE:
Whoa!
No, no, no, no, no!
( high pitched squeals )
I've never gone
this fast before.
Phoebe, forget it.
Okay?
Newark is like, an hour away.
There's no way we're going
to make it in time.
She's got her cell.
You could call her.
I am not doing this
over the phone.
You don't have any other choice.
( screams )
( cell phone rings )
Hello?
Rachel.
Oh, good!
Hey, by the way, did you just
get on the plane?
Yeah.
For what it's worth,
we would've caught her
if we were at
the right airport.
Yay.
Rach, hang on.
( mouthing words )
Phoebe, is everything okay?
Um... actually, no.
No, you have to
get off the plane.
What? Why?
I have this feeling
that something's wrong with it.
Something is wrong with
the left, filangee.
Oh, honey, I'm sure there's
nothing wrong with the plane.
All right, look,
I have to go.
I love you,
and I will call you
the minute I get to Paris.
Um... what was that?
Oh, that was just
my crazy friend.
She told me I should
get off the plane
because she had a feeling
that there was something wrong
with the left filangee.
Okay, that doesn't
sound good.
I wouldn't worry about it.
She's always coming up
with stuff like this.
And you know what,
she's almost never right.
But she is sometimes?
Well...?
What are you doing?
Well, I can't
take this plane now.
Excuse me, sir?
Where you going?
I have to get off
this plane, okay?
Her friend has a feeling
something's wrong
with the left filangee.
Could I get some peanuts?
What's wrong with the plane?
There's nothing wrong
with the plane.
The left filangee.
There's no filangee.
Oh, my God.
This plane doesn't even
have a filangee.
Well, then I'm not
flying on it.
Ma'am, please sit down.
What's going on?
We're all getting off.
There is no filangee!
This is ridiculous. I...
Yeah, okay.
( chirping )
( sighing ):
All right.
My job here is done.
That was... impressive.
Y-Yeah. You didn't even use
the tools for most of it.
Eh, they were just
slowing me down.
All right, I got to
get back to the babies.
See you girls later.
Sorry about the table, man.
Yeah.
You going to buy a new one?
Probably not.
No.
I don't know how much I'm going
to want to play after you go.
Well, at least we got
these little guys out.
Yeah.
Oh! We were worried
about you.
Hmm.
Guess I better get used to
things crapping in my hand, huh?
Oh, I'm going to miss
these little guys.
It was nice
having birds around again.
Hey, you know what?
Maybe we should keep
them here with you.
What?
Yeah. I mean, we've got
a lot going on right now.
And plus, here, they'd
have their own room.
I could get a goose!
You know, I think you're
set with the poultry.
Thanks, man.
You hear that, you guys?
You're going to get
to stay here.
And-and it's good, you know?
'Cause, uh...
'cause now you have
a reason to come visit.
I think there may be
another reason.
So, uh...
awkward hug or lame,
cool-guy handshake.
( clears throat ):
Yeah, well, you know,
lame, cool-guy handshake.
Doo-doo-doo-doo!
Ma'am I assure you,
the plane is fine.
And you fixed the filangee?
Yes, the filangee is fixed.
As a matter of fact,
we put a whole lot
of extra filangees on board,
just in case.
Where is she?
I don't see her.
Rachel!
Rachel Greene!
There she is!
Rachel! Rachel!
Whoa, whoa, excuse me, sir.
Do you have a boarding pass?
No, no, I just
have to talk to someone
that's getting on
the plane.
I'm sorry, sir.
You cannot go any further
without a boarding pass.
No, no, no. But I...
You don't understand...
Rachel!
What?
Oh, my God. What are you...?
What are you guys doing here?
Okay. You're on.
What? What, Ross?
Okay, you're scaring me.
What's going on?
Okay.
The thing is...
Yeah?
Don't go.
What?
Please, please
stay with me.
I am so in love with you.
Please don't go.
Oh, my God.
I know. I know.
I shouldn't have waited
till now to say it,
but, um... that
was stupid, okay?
I'm sorry, but
I'm telling you now.
I love you.
Do not get on this plane.
Miss?
I...
Are you boarding
the plane?
Hey, hey.
I know you love me.
I know you do.
Miss?
I... I...
I have to get on the plane.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
I do. They're waiting
for me, Ross.
I can't do this right now.
I'm sorry.
Rachel?
( half-whispers ):
I'm so sorry.
I really thought she'd stay.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Oh!
( sobs )
Well...
that's it.
Everything's packed.
Wow.
This is weird.
I know.
Yeah.
Uh, does this mean
there's nothing to eat?
I put three lasagnas
in your freezer.
I love you.
Hey.
Hey, so, did you guys
make it in time?
Yeah, yeah.
He talked to her.
But, um, she got
on the plane, anyway.
Where's Ross?
He went home.
He didn't want to see anybody.
Oh.
( beeps )
RACHEL:
Ross, hi.
It's me.
I just got back on the plane,
and I just feel awful.
That is so not how I wanted
things to end with us.
It's... it's just that I...
wasn't expecting to see you,
and then all of a sudden
you're there
and saying these things.
And... now I'm just sitting here
and thinking
of all the stuff I should have
said and I didn't.
I mean, I didn't even get to
tell you that I love you, too.
Because of course I do.
I love you.
What am I doing?
( sighs ):
I've got to see you.
I've got to get off this plane.
Oh, my God.
RACHEL:
Okay, ex-excuse me.
WOMAN:
Miss, please,
sit down!
No, I'm sorry,
I'm really sorry.
But I need to get
off the plane, okay?
I need to just tell someone
that I love them.
Miss, I can't let you
off the plane.
Let her off the plane!
I am afraid you are going
to have to take your seat.
Oh, please.
Miss, you don't
understand.
Try to understand!
Oh, come on, Miss.
Isn't there any way
that you can just
let me off the...?
( beeps )
No, no!
Oh, my God.
Did she get off the plane?
I got off the plane.
You got off the plane.
I do love you.
Oh!
I love you, too, and I am
never letting you go again.
Okay, 'cause this
is where I want to be.
Okay? No more messing around.
I don't want to
mess this up again.
Me, neither. Okay? We are...
we're done being stupid.
Okay.
It's you and me,
all right? This is it.
This is it.
Unless we're on a break.
Don't make jokes now.
Okay, please be careful
with that.
It was my grandmother's.
Be careful.
Thank you.
Uh, if that falls off
the truck, it wouldn't
be the worst thing.
Wow.
I know.
It seems smaller somehow.
Hmm.
Has it always been purple?
Look around, you guys.
This was your first home.
And it was a happy place--
filled with love and laughter,
but more important,
because of rent control,
it was a friggin' steal.
Hey, do you realize
that at one time or another,
we all lived
in this apartment?
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Uh, I haven't.
Wait a minute.
What about
that summer
during college that you
lived with Grandma
and you tried to
make it as a dancer?
Do you realize we
almost made it ten years
without that coming up?
Oh, honey,
I forgot.
I promised Treeger
that we'd leave our keys.
Oh, okay.
( sighs )
So, I guess this is it.
Yeah.
I guess so.
( voice breaking ):
This is harder
than I thought
it would be.
Oh, it's going to be okay.
Okay.
( sniffling )
Do you guys have to go
to the new house right away,
or do you have some time?
We got some time.
Okay, should we get
some coffee?
Sure.
Okay.
Where?
( half-whispers ):
Oh, thanks, guys.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org